You Were Never Really Here is a crime, drama,
thriller film directed by Lynne Ramsay.
A traumatized veteran, unafraid of violence, tracks
down missing girls for a living.
When a job spins out of control, his nightmares begin to overtake him, and a conspiracy
is uncovered—leading to what may be his death trip or his awakening.
Joe, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Joe's Mother, played by Judith Roberts.
Nina Votto, played by Ekaterina Samsonov.
John McCleary, played by John Doman.
Senator Albert Votto, played by Alex Manette.
Young Joe, played by Dante Pereira-Olson.
You Were Never Really Here (released as A Beautiful Day in France and Germany) is a 2017
neo-noir crime psychological thriller film written and directed by Lynne Ramsay.
Based on the 2013 novella of the same name by Jonathan Ames, it stars Joaquin
Phoenix, Ekaterina Samsonov, Alex Manette, John Doman, and Judith Roberts.
In the film, a traumatized mercenary named Joe (Phoenix) is hired by a politician to find and rescue his daughter who has been
kidnapped by a human trafficking network in New York City, which Joe is instructed to destroy by any violent means.
The film was co-produced between the United Kingdom and France.
An early cut premiered at the 2017 Cannes Film Festival in competition, where Ramsay
won the award for Best Screenplay and Phoenix the award for Best Actor.
The film was released by StudioCanal in the UK, on 9 March 2018, and by Amazon Studios in the U.S., where it
began a limited release in Los Angeles and New York on 6 April 2018, and a wide release on 20 April.
It received critical acclaim, with Ramsay's direction and
Phoenix's performance garnering high praise.
The film explores themes of hotel, new york city, post-traumatic stress
disorder (ptsd), based on novel or book, childhood trauma.
The tone is emotional and intense.